bestfares.com 2009-03-09

# Best Fares.com :. Cheap discount airfares, Cheap discount flights, Cheap discount tickets, Cheap discount cruises

Bestfares.com (Bestfares U.S.A., Inc.) respects your privacy. Bestfares.com provides this statement to inform you about the privacy policy for the Bestfares.com site ("Site") and choices you may make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice may be accessed from throughout the Site.

The Bestfares.com site is designed so that you may visit it without identifying yourself or revealing your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"), which can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Access to some portions of the Site requires a paid membership. Once you choose to provide Personal Information, it only will be used to support your customer relationship with Bestfares.com.

**Information Collected and How it is Used**

On some Bestfares.com pages, you may register to receive a periodic e-mail about travel-related offers or initiate a paid membership with Bestfares.com. The types of Personal Information collected may include an e-mail address, postal code, name, physical address and credit card account number and expiration date.

From time to time, Bestfares.com also may use your Personal Information to provide you with marketing offers or to contact you for the purpose of market research. Bestfares.com will give you the opportunity to decline such solicitations and will do everything possible to honor such requests.

Bestfares.com will not sell or lease Personal Information to third parties. Unless Bestfares.com has your permission or is required by law, it only will share your Personal Information with vendors and other suppliers of products or services to Bestfares members (such as an airline) to fulfill a purchase request authorized by you.

Bestfares.com uses data collected online, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and other non-personally identifiable information, in aggregate to analyze trends, administer the Site and gather broad demographic information. The aggregated information will not be associated in any way that can identify you individually. Bestfares.com reserves the right to share aggregated information about users of the Site with parties outside of Bestfares.com, including vendors and business associates.

Be aware that Bestfares.com may publish links on the Site that connect to external Web sites, which may collect personal information about you. This statement does not cover privacy practices or policies of Web sites external to Bestfares.com. Bestfares.com provides this notice so that users can make informed choices about sharing personal information with other Web sites.

**Choice and Changes**

Bestfares.com users are given the opportunity to modify their Personal Information by contacting the customer service department at custserve@bestfares.com. Users who no longer wish to receive the Bestfares.com e-mail newsletter may terminate that services by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of each e-mail newsletter or by e-mailing a request to custserve@bestfares.com.

Physical address or billing information may be updated by calling the Bestfares.com Membership Department at 1-800-880-1234. You also may e-mail updates to custserve@bestfares.com.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's local computer containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any Personal Information while on the Site. If a user rejects a cookie, he or she may still use the Site, but some portions of the Site, such as the Members-Only section, may not be accessible.

Some Bestfares.com vendors and advertisers use cookies on the Site. However, Bestfares.com has no access to, or control over, these cookies, and any information contained in these cookies may not store personally identifiable information.

**Security**

Bestfares.com takes precautions to protect users' Personal Information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, Bestfares.com has established reasonable procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected online. Bestfares.com uses industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) when collecting or transferring sensitive data, such as credit card information.

**Statement Updates**

Bestfares.com may update this policy in the future to address new services that may be added to the Site. Please review the privacy policy from time to time to note revisions. If this policy is changed in a material way, Bestfares.com will post notice of the change on the Site and notify you via e-mail at the address you have provided prior to the change. If any proposed change is unacceptable to you, you may request that your Personal Information be removed.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, you may contact Bestfares.com at privacy@bestfares.com. Bestfares.com will attempt to respond to your query within five business days of receipt.
